<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2012-11-09T16:09:38-06:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>mobile_beta_apps</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/mobile-beta-apps.html"/>
   <updated>2012-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/mobile-beta-apps</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We have Android and iPhone apps available to distribute to our beta users! These are not yet in the stores.. so to get them to you it takes a couple steps. It's simple, but please make sure to follow the steps precisely to make sure your app works :).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Android&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1. Download this.
Step 2. Enable applications downloaded from websites in developer options
Step 3. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iPhone / iPod touch&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Email us your device ID.
a. Connect your phone and launch iTunes.
b. Click your device from the left sidebar
c. Click where it says &quot;Serial Number&quot;, which turns it into Identifier (UDID)
d. Copy this 40-character string and email it to info(at)hoos.in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 2: We send you an email with a pre-release app in a day or two&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 3: Download and install the App&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. Download the zip file from our email&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. unzip the file.. there will be a '.ipa' file and a '.mobileprovision' file&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. drag-and-drop both file into the Applications folder in your iTunes library&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;d. in iTunes, select your device and open the Applications tab. Sync applications with the hoos.in app checked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;e. Sync your iPhone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 4: Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>More Social, Less Network</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/more-social-less-network.html"/>
   <updated>2012-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/more-social-less-network</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here's the deal. There are a lot of people in the world, we're all really connected, and most of us want to lead a kick-ass social life full of creativity and adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means on any given day, in any city, there are a bunch of people you already know that want to do something great; rock a jam session, host a luau, climb a mountain and watch the sunrise, play pick-up, learn to paint. But for most of us that only happens once in a while. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are busy. Coordinating an awesome idea takes a lot of work, and there's nothing that just does it for us. We get home from work drained, and we have to call  have to share it with the right people, plan for numbers, give directions, tell ppl what to bring, collect everyone's share... Pretty soon, our dream of naked feather-pillow-fighting on the rooftop at sunset turns into just another stressful to-do item, and we give up living a mini-adventure every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That's a tragedy. A life full of new relationships and experiences makes us healthier, sexier, smarter, happier and just about any other-ier. Plus it's good old fashioned fun. So what can we do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can remove the hassle and make living an extraordinary social life ordinary. We can use technology to enable real social life instead of virtualizing it. And we can do great things with friends every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a social network that's More Social and Less Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to hoos.in.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>